Otto Rothschild Photographic Archive LSC.1381
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Negative Nos. V10-V1400, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 401)
- Negative Nos. V1405-V2798, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 402)
- Negative Nos. V2803-V3898, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 403)
- Negative Nos. V3908-V5100, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 404)
- Negative Nos. V5201-V5995, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 405)
- Negative Nos. V6006-V7000, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 406)
- Negative Nos. V7002-V8095, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 407)
- Negative Nos. V8103-V8997, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 408)
- Negative Nos. V9003-V9799, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 409)
- Negative Nos. V9800-W698, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 410)
- Negative Nos. W706-W1499, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 411)
- Negative Nos. W1500-W2298, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 412)
- Negative Nos. W2302-W2996, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 413)
- Negative Nos. W3000-W3799, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 414)
- Negative Nos. W3804-W4499, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 415)
- Negative Nos. W4500-W5297, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 416)
- Negative Nos. W5300-W6199, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 417)
- Negative Nos. W6200-W7096, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 418)
- Negative Nos. W7100-W8098, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 419)
- Negative Nos. W8100-W9099, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 420)
- Negative Nos. W9100-W9981, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 421)
- Negative Nos. X1-X999, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 422)
- Negative Nos. X1000-X1899, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 423)
- Negative Nos. X1900-X2696, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 424)
- Negative Nos. X2700-X3498, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 425)
- Negative Nos. X3500-X4188, 2 × 10 negative strips (Box 426)
- Negative Nos. E1201-N7961, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 427)
- Negative Nos. N8067-R8139, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 428)
- Negative Nos. R8223-T6228, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 429)
- Negative Nos. T6264-V2529, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 430)
- Negative Nos. V2638-V6476, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 431)
- Negative Nos. V6494-V8550, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 432)
- Negative Nos. V8551-W2557, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 433)
- Negative Nos. W2608-W5589, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 434)
- Negative Nos. W5590-W8315, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 435)
- Negative Nos. W8389-X1498, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 436)
- Negative Nos. X1539-X4187, 1 × 9 negative strips (Box 437)
- Negative Nos. A-W1737, 8 × 10 negatives (Box 438)
- Negative Nos. W2636-46728, 8 × 10 negatives (Box 439)
- Negative Nos. 44994-128952, 8 × 10 negatives (Box 440)
- All, 5 × 7 negatives (Box 441)
- 1938 - 1939 (Box 442)
- 1938 - 1939, 1939 - 1941 (Box 443)
- A - B (Box 444)
- C - H (Box 445)
- Hollywood Democratic Committee - K (Box 446)
- L + Modern Forum (Box 447)
- M + Mays & Bennett (Box 448)
- Mt. Sinai (Box 449)
- M - P (Box 450)
- P - R (Box 451)
- R - T (Box 452)
- T - W (Box 453)
- Victory House + California Pension Plan (Box 454)
- Don Lee Mutual (Box 455, Box 456, Box 457, Box 458, Box 459)
- Don Lee Mutual + Pan Pacific Auditorium (Box 460)
- War Chest + "Hey Rookie!" (Box 461)
- "Hey Rookie!" (including contact prints) (Box 462)
- Treasury department (Box 463)
- Treasury Department + USO (Box 464)
- USO (Box 465)
- USO + Light Opera (Box 466)
- Light Opera + Family, weddings & others. (Box 467)
- Family, weddings & others + L.A. Press Photographers Association (Box 468)
- American Legion (Box 469)
- Photographs by Bill Harvey [?] (Box 470)
- 12 reels 35mm. Lytton Home Loan Negs: R4686. Neg Reels 95923, 617EC13, 12001, 16170 (Box 471)
- Tropics, Little Fuse Inc., Swan Party, Haire Publications, KECA (Box 472)
- Prudential (Box 473)
- Jack Berman (Box 474)
- Jack Lalanne (Box 475)
- Ephemera and miscellaneous negatives (Box 476)
- Slides for the Music Center (Box 477)
- Various 4x5 and 5x7 negatives (to be filed?) Including H.G. Wells (Box 478)
- Negative Nos. A1830-D9857, 35mm. negatives (Box 479)
- Ephemera (Box 480, Box 481)
- Work order sheets (Box 482)
- Negative Nos. 37842-70871, Card index (Box 483)
- Negative Nos. 70872-76111, Card index (Box 484)
- Negative Nos. 76112-82400, Card index (Box 485)
- Negative Nos. 82401-83314, Card index (Box 486)
- Negative Nos. 83315-94719, Card index (Box 487)
- Negative Nos. 94720-99992, Card index (Box 488)
- Negative Nos. 99993-106869, Card index (Box 489)
- Negative Nos. 106873-113834, Card index (Box 490)
- Negative Nos. 113835-120564, Card index (Box 491)
- Negative Nos. 120565-127402, Card index (Box 492)
- Negative Nos. 127403-133379, Card index (Box 493)
- Negative Nos. 133380-A1856, Card index (Box 494)
- Negative Nos. A1857-A8939, Card index (Box 495)
- Negative Nos. A8940-B6593, Card index (Box 496)
- Negative Nos. B6594-C3511, Card index (Box 497)
- Negative Nos. C3634-D1, Card index (Box 498)
- Negative Nos. D2-D5909, Card index (Box 499)
- Negative Nos. D5910-E2399, Card index (Box 500)
- Negative Nos. E2400-E8545, Card index (Box 501)
- Negative Nos. E8546-H4929, Card index (Box 502)
- Negative Nos. H4930-L1506, Card index (Box 503)
- Negative Nos. L1507-L7509, Card index (Box 504)
- Negative Nos. L7510-N3903, Card index (Box 505)
- Negative Nos. N3904-P727, Card index (Box 506)
- Negative Nos. P728-P6977, Card index (Box 507)
- Negative Nos. P6978-R2372, Card index (Box 508)
- Negative Nos. R2373-R7841, Card index (Box 509)
- Negative Nos. R7842-S4096, Card index (Box 510)
- Negative Nos. S4097-T599, Card index (Box 511)
- Negative Nos. T600-T6799, Card index (Box 512)
- Negative Nos. T6800-V605, Card index (Box 513)
- Negative Nos. V606-V2300, Card index (Box 514)
- Negative Nos. V2301-V3939, Card index (Box 515)
- Negative Nos. V3940-V5750, Card index (Box 516)
- Negative Nos. V5751-V7842, Card index (Box 517)
- Negative Nos. V7825-W69, Card index (Box 518)
- Negative Nos. W74-W2690, Card index (Box 519)
- Negative Nos. W2691-W5000, Card index (Box 520)
- Negative Nos. W5001-W7599, Card index (Box 521)
- Negative Nos. W7600-CX290, Card index (Box 522)
- Negative Nos. CX291-CX2724, Card index (Box 523)
- Negative Nos. CX2725-X0123, Card index (Box 524)
- Correspondence & periodicals (Box 525)
- Catalogues & technical materials (Box 526)
- Technical manuals and books (Box 527)
- Brochures, catalogues and technical materials (Box 528)
- Professional organizations, including correspondence and various papers (Box 529)
- Brochures, catalogues, notes, periodicals and ephemera (Box 530)
- Photographs (Box 531)
- Photographs, periodicals and film (Box 532)
- Film (Box 533)
- Film & Downtown Businessmen's Association contestant fact sheets and notes (Box 534)
- Downtown Businessmen's Association contestant photographs and notes (Box 535)
- Photographs; Payroll - 1964; Journal - 1962; workorder sheets for job numbers (Box 536)
- Mounted photographs (Box 537)
- Technical manuals (Box 538)
- Technical manuals (Box 539)
- Buyers handbooks; catalogs; "A work day in the life of a camp boy" by Russell Doehrer (Box 540)
- AAAA-Bowyer - client card index (Box 541)
- AAAA-Bower, J.W. - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 541)
- Bradley Dinner Committee-Capitol Records (Vickie Youn) - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 542)
- Caples Co.-Dow Chemical Co. - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 543)
- Downtown Bus. Men's Ass'n-The Group - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 544)
- Gruen Watch Co.-KTLA - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 545)
- KTTV - Inc.-The Los Angeles Club - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 546)
- L.A. Convention Cent.-Mullins- Earl Adv. - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 547)
- Multiple Sclerosis Society-Pyne, Joe - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 548)
- Rothschild, Otto-Sister Magdelene Mary - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 549)
- Siteman, Bernie-Veterans Service Center - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 550)
- Vibration Research-Zukor-Forsher Productions - client card index, Card index of client names (Box 551)
- Negative Nos. A-Z - client card index, 3 sequences of client names not interfiled into general index (Box 552)